export const introPythonExercise = {
  title: 'Introduction to Python â€“ Exercise',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Python is a _____ level programming language.',
      options: ['Low', 'Middle', 'High', 'Machine'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Python is known for its?',
      options: ['Complex syntax', 'Speed only', 'Readability', 'Compilation'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Python code blocks are defined using?',
      options: ['Brackets', 'Semicolons', 'Indentation', 'Parentheses'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Which symbol is used for comments in Python?',
      options: ['//', '#', '/* */', '--'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Python is _____ language.',
      options: ['Compiled', 'Interpreted', 'Machine', 'Assembly'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which company uses Python?',
      options: ['Google', 'Facebook', 'Netflix', 'All'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Python was created by?',
      options: ['Dennis Ritchie', 'James Gosling', 'Guido van Rossum', 'Bjarne Stroustrup'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Python is best suited for?',
      options: ['Web only', 'Games only', 'Data science', 'All domains'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Python files are saved with extension?',
      options: ['.java', '.py', '.js', '.c'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Python programs are easy to?',
      options: ['Debug', 'Write', 'Read', 'All'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
  ],
}